[GUNSHOTS]
Elizabeth! Hey! What's going on?
Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
nezumiiro no sora no shita
Higawari no chizu
ikutsumo no yume ga nijinde ita
Itsuka wa sa chippoke na
boku no kono hohaba demo
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
Tsuyogatte kizutsuita kokoro sukashita you ni
Furidashita amatsubutachi ga
ranhansha kurikaesu
Massugu na hikari ga kousa shite
Yukusaki mo tsugenu mama
dokomademo tsukinukeru
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakistukete
Kono sora no shita donna toko ni ite mo
Todoku hazu nanda mada minu sekai e
Subtitles from Mohamed610 corrected by somanypetals.
So this piece of info was
supposed to be confidential...
...but, whatever.
Barry told me the Colonel's got a plan
to smoke out some military guys he's been after.
The ones from "The Fifth" something or other.
The Fifth Laboratory.
Al?
I gotta find him.
This could lead us straight to the
person who killed Lieutenant Hughes.
Huh?!
Hey, not so fast!
Tell me your secret first!
I'll tell you when I get back, okay?
Oh, come on! That's so unfair!
I'll be back soon.
Okay. Just be careful.
I will. I promise.
[GUN CLICKING EMPTY]
Are you all done now?
Then it's time to eat you.
[BARKING]
[GROWLING]
Stop it! That tickles!
Catch!
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUN CLICKING EMPTY]
Bullets gone? Goodie, goodie!
I get to have dinner and dessert!
I barely made it.
[RELIEVED EXHALE]
Colonel!
Why the hell did you leave your post?!
Uh—!
No matter what happened to us, you could
still have kept your involvement a secret!
That was the whole idea, right?
But you just come waltzing in here, plain as day!
Are you a complete idiot?!
MUSTANG: Yeah, fine, fine, that's it. I'm an idiot, happy?
[FUERY CHUCKLING]
Who the heck was that fat guy?
Colonel! The target's on the move, sir!
Strike the camp, sergeant!
Don't leave a single trace!
And you stay right by the
sergeant's side, Hayate Sir!
- Sir!
- [BARKS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Colonel.
What is it?
Thanks for saving us back there.
Tell me later.
Let's just stay focused on the mission for now.
Sir.
Quick, get in!
Yes, sir.
Are you trying to go after
Mr. Hughes' murderer?
You in?
Yeah!
Don't let him get away.
He ain't going nowhere.
[LAUGHS]
My soul won't be able to rest.
Not until I eviscerate that meatbag!
So do you think we can expect another
appearance from that blubberbeast back there?
I doubt it. I scorched him off the ledge.
Yeah, and I shot him in the head,
but he didn't really seem to mind.
[GASPS]
He didn't have an Ouroboros tattoo, did he?
A tattoo? Well...
Actually, yeah. On his tongue.
In that case, you were probably dealing with a Homunculus.
[BARRY SCREAMING]
Watch it, Mustang!
Hold on a damn second.
What are you saying, Al?
That's just not possible.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Until I got kidnapped by a Homunculus.
He called himself Greed.
One thing he told me
is that nothing is impossible.
I know for a fact that they
have amazing healing powers.
I watched Greed get the top half of his head knocked off,
but he was perfectly fine a minute later.
They're real, all right.
But I understand if you don't believe me.
After what I just saw, I have to believe you.
Hold on, I rendered Fatboy down
to a bubbling puddle back there.
Are you telling me he's still alive?
AL: Probably.
MUSTANG: Tch. Wonderful!
Just a never-ending
parade of freaks lately, huh?
BARRY: My body ran in there.
Seems to think it can hide from me.
MUSTANG: The Third Laboratory, huh?
So this ties them directly to the military.
That's all we need for now.
We're pulling back.
BARRY: Well, you have fun with that!
MUSTANG: Get back here!
HAVOC: That psycho stormed the building.
Yep, it's our lucky day.
Huh?
[BARRY GIGGLING MANIACALLY]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Out of my way!
I don't want any of your boring old skin and bones.
I got me a special reunion to get to.
All personnel must evacuate immediately!
Um, Colonel?
Stay back. The man who broke in is a deranged murderer.
My men will handle his capture.
Order your guards to seal off the exits!
Yes, sir!
HAVOC: How the hell are we
supposed to find him?
We're gonna have to split up.
Yes, sir.
It doesn't look like anybody's
used this lab in a while.
I guess not. What is this stuff?
I have no idea.
But whatever they did here
was painful for someone.
Well now,
I am just shocked.
It's bad enough that you
stood me up on our date.
And now you point a gun at me?
You've got some nerve,
don't you?
Solaris?
What's going on?
Hey, Havoc...
Your girl's got the tattoo.
HAVOC: Yeah. First I've seen it, sir.
Quit staring.
It's not very polite.
MUSTANG: Well, I can see how
she tricked you so easily.
You've always been
a sucker for big boobs.
[CRYING] I can't help it! I love 'em!
Did you tell this woman anything?
No. I never said a single
thing about work, sir!
Tell me. Do you know who Maes Hughes is?
Oh, yes. He was quite the
intelligent man, wouldn't you agree?
I only wish I'd had the opportunity to pick his brain
[GUNSHOT]
On your knees!
I wanna know everything.
Sorry to say...
But it's gonna take more than you're
capable of to make me get on my—
[GUNSHOTS]
How merciless. Did you pick that up in Ishval, huh?
You're a Homunculus.
Indeed. How very astute of you, Jean.
But I doubt you've seen this one.
Take a good look, boys. It's a Philosopher's Stone.
I was created with this stone at my core.
It's not just a legend, it's my heart.
You're a monster.
That was uncalled for.
I do have feelings.
Apart from a few things, I was
made nearly identical to you.
I am human.
MUSTANG: I've got a funny feeling the
only reason you're telling us this...
is because you don't
plan on letting us live.
Yep. It's such a shame.
Too slow!
Oh no, did I get your
ignition glove all wet?
Silly me.
[BOTH YELLING]
What are we gonna do? She'll shred us with her freaky fingers!
No, she made a big mistake.
She flooded the room with water.
A simple transmutation
and we've got hydrogen gas.
[BOTH GASP]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
HAVOC: Aw...
Crap. This was a gift from
one of my ex-girlfriends.
Man.
Hey, Colonel.
You mind giving me a light here?
Oh, right. You're all wet.
Yeah, well those things will
kill you, you know that?!
She's dust. I definitely cremated her.
How do you know for sure, sir?
The stench.
I'm pretty familiar with that stink by now.
You mean from that
time you spent in Ishval?
For all we know, she
could still regenerate.
So stay alert.
Yes, sir.
Ah!
Havoc!
MUSTANG: Havoc, hang in there.
LUST: Don't kid yourself.
[LAUGHS]
He's a dead man.
No, he's not.
Give up.
There's nothing you can do that'll kill me.
Then you won't mind if I borrow this!
I need it to save Havoc.
I don't know that much about medicinal alchemy,
but this should amplify my abilities.
It seems like you should buy a girl dinner first,
before you stick your hand in her chest.
Uh...your Excellency!
What's the current status?
The criminal responsible for the
prison break has stormed the premises.
But Colonel Mustang
and his men are in pursuit.
Well then, I'll give him some backup.
Very good. We're right behind you, sir.
No.
I'd prefer to handle it on my own.
[LAUGHS]
I told you.
The Philosopher's Stone's my core.
I really hate to do this.
You were a prime
candidate for sacrifice and all.
But you forced me to kill you.
God damn you.
[GLOVE TEARING]
Save your breath.
I want you to watch
poor Jean bleed to death.
Then you can die.
Jean.
Hey.
Answer me.
Havoc!
You can't die.
Not yet. Not before I do.
Havoc...
BARRY: Sorry.
But you got here too late.
Look at this mess.
My body is damn near entirely decayed.
I guess a body just can't hold up with
someone else's soul being shoved inside of it.
[AL GASPS]
If a soul is incompatible
with another person's body...
wouldn't it be the same for a
soul bonded to a suit of armor?
If that's right...
There's no guarantee I'll be able to stay in
this form long enough to get our old bodies back.
Brother.
I was wondering when you
were going to show up, Lusty.
Number 66.
Care to explain why
you're helping the Colonel?
I thought it'd be fun to switch things up.
Besides, I've wanted to
chop you up since I met you.
You're such a handful, 66.
And I'm sad to see you here, Armor Boy.
You just had to tag along.
Talk about a setback.
It's bad enough to lose one, but now you're
forcing me to kill a second candidate.
AL: Candidate?
A second one?
Yeah.
You and Mr. Gallantry.
That's enough of the
casual chit-chat, Lust!
All I want to hear from you is screaming!
I do hate overconfident men.
Now then, where were we?
I think I was about to send the
Lieutenant to join her superior.
[GASPS]
Wait a minute.
So when you said you'd already
had to kill someone...
It can't be.
You didn't!
[CHUCKLES]
[GASPS]
You bitch!
[CONTINUOUS GUNFIRE]
[HAWKEYE SCREAMING]
[GUN CLICKING EMPTY]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[HAWKEYE SOBBING]
[GUN CLICKS EMPTY]
Are you done?
Such a sad and weak creature.
Another typical human.
Stand up, Lieutenant. You need to get out of here.
LUST: Do you want me to kill you first?
[GASPS]
Oh my.
It appears you've opened the portal.
Such a shame.
You are a perfect candidate.
HAWKEYE: Listen, Alphonse,
leave me and save yourself.
AL: No!
Run!
- I won't!
- Go!
I won't leave you!
I'm sick of watching people die, and I
can't just sit back and take it anymore!
I won't let anyone else get killed!
Not when I can protect them!
Well spoken.
I couldn't agree more.
[GASP]
[LUST SCREAMING]
MUSTANG: Looks like I can get you
on your knees, after all.
LUST: He's using the flint for ignition...
And he carved a
transmutation circle into his hand!
You should have bled
to death by now!
I seared the wound closed.
I came close to passing out from the pain.
You told me I couldn't kill you.
But I'd like to try
and prove you wrong!
So let's see.
How many times is it gonna take?
[LUST SCREAMING]
Colonel!
[LUST SCREAMING] No!
[LUST SCREAMING]
You killed me.
I hate losing.
But there are worse ways to die
than at the hands of a man like you.
I love how cold and
focused your eyes are.
I look forward...
to the day when those eyes will be wide with agony.
It's coming.
It's coming...
Colonel!
Are you alright?
Forget about me.
We need to get you some help.
Thanks, Alphonse.
Thank you for looking
after my subordinate.
Yeah, sure.
We need to call you a doctor.
Oh, yeah. Hurry.
Call a doctor for Havoc.
Please.
He's alright... He's alright...
[GASP]
Uh, hey.
I'm home now.
Moron! Welcome back!
Uh...okay! Thanks?
Well...uh...
[WINRY LAUGHING]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[CRASH]
[BOTH YELLING]
WINRY: That shouldn't happen!
AL: It won't stay!
AL: Ah! I can't put it back on!
BARRY: Holy moly!
That was way too damn close.
I hope someone can fix me.
I'd rather not live
my life as sheet metal.
Ahh—what the...
How the hell are you still alive?!
Hey! Oh, no!
Put me down right now!
I-I've got a second
chance to terrorize the city!
You're gonna ruin everything!
No! Don't do it! Wait!
No! Stop! Please!
[BARRY'S BODY THUDS]
[INDISCERNIBLE]
[TWINKLE]
It can't be...
Is it?
[GASPS]
Hohenheim!
Let it all out, let it all out
Tsuyogaranakute ii n da ne
Dareka ga kaite'tta
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
Jibunrashisa nante, dare mo wakaranai yo
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu
de nakushitari, hirottari,
Kyuu ni samishiku natte,
naichau hi mo aru kedo
Namida mo itami mo, hoshi ni kaeyou
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
Chiisana te kazashite
futari de tsukurou hoshikuzu wo
Tsuyoku hikaru ein wo
Sayonara itsuka wa kuru ka mo shirenu
Kisetsu wa sore demo meguri megutte'ku
Chiisaku mayotte mo aruite'ku
Kimi to aruite'ku
Sore daku wa kawaranaide iyou ne
The truth stands between
two opposing mirrors,
each casting reflections
of outrage and joy.
When unexpectedly
confronted by his forsaken past,
the young man is forced to resolve issues
that have laid hidden within
the shadows of his anger.
Next time on Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode 20: Father Before the Grave.
It's not necessary to shed tears.
A person can still cry without them.